Welcome to the release presentation of VoltAudit AI.
VoltAudit AI is an enterprise-grade utility bill auditing platform
designed to identify pricing discrepancies and prevent payment losses.
Utility invoices in enterprise environments are highly complex and prone to errors.
Discrepancies in rates, peak hours, and duplicate billings lead to millions in losses.
Auditing these manually is slow and prone to oversight.
VoltAudit AI addresses this through a decoupled, multi-layered architecture.
A FastAPI backend processes requests, exposing tools to the frontend.
The data access layer is strictly isolated behind Model Context Protocol stdio interfaces.
This guards the underlying SQLite database from direct external access.
The core reasoning engine is built around Google's Agent Development Kit,
coordinating an active workforce of eight specialized agents.
From ingestion and vendor resolution to duplicate checks,
each worker acts sequentially, communicating through a shared execution context.
Let's see the system in action using the Streamlit dashboard interface.
We submit a clean utility invoice, and progress indicators track each agent.
The system resolves all checks successfully, grading the run with a perfect score.
When a dirty invoice containing math errors is uploaded, the reconciler flags it.
The risk specialist weighs the deviations, immediately triggering a human approval gateway.
Under the Human Review Queue, administrators inspect the flagged discrepancies.
An operator must write a valid justification text parsed by our governance override skill.
Only approved justifications can bypass the hold and update the status.
VoltAudit AI is fully containerized and production-ready.
With pre-commit quality gates, rigorous type-safety, and local load test validation,
the repository ensures zero downtime and absolute stability.
VoltAudit AI combines enterprise multi-agent ADK systems with a secure architecture.
Delivering intelligent utility cost control. Thank you.